{
  "science": {
    "0": {
      "question": "Which of these reduces friction?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "car brakes",
        "1": "tire tread",
        "2": "ball bearings",
        "3": "sandpaper"
      },
      "answer": "ball bearings"
    },
    "1": {
      "question": "Which of these undergoes metamorphosis?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "butterfly",
        "1": "bacteria",
        "2": "snake",
        "3": "chicken"
      },
      "answer": "butterfly"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "Which of these is the best explanation of how a smooth round stone became smooth?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "continuous freezing and thawing",
        "1": "volcanic action",
        "2": "It fell off the side of a cliff.",
        "3": "It was in a stream for a long time."
      },
      "answer": ""
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "Mollusks typically have",
      "choices": {
        "0": "wings",
        "1": "shells",
        "2": "scales",
        "3": "backbones"
      },
      "answer": "shells"
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "Water droplets forming on the inside of a cold windshield is an example of",
      "choices": {
        "0": "evaporation",
        "1": "conduction",
        "2": "vaporization",
        "3": "condensation"
      },
      "answer": "condensation"
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "Marrow is a soft tissue found in the",
      "choices": {
        "0": "brain",
        "1": "bones",
        "2": "muscles",
        "3": "ligaments"
      },
      "answer": "bones"
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "Weight is a measure of a body’s",
      "choices": {
        "0": "energy",
        "1": "momentum",
        "2": "rotational equilibrium",
        "3": "gravitational attraction to the Earth"
      },
      "answer": "gravitational attraction to the Earth"
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "Which of these systems enable oxygen to reach an individual cell in the human body?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "digestive",
        "1": "circulatory",
        "2": "nervous",
        "3": "excretory"
      },
      "answer": "circulatory"
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "The changing of any kind of matter from one form to another absorbs or releases",
      "choices": {
        "0": "dust",
        "1": "inertia",
        "2": "gravity",
        "3": "energy"
      },
      "answer": "energy"
    },
    "9": {
      "question": "Citrus fruits include",
      "choices": {
        "0": "apples",
        "1": "oranges",
        "2": "bananas",
        "3": "peaches"
      },
      "answer": "oranges"
    },
    "10": {
      "question": "An example of kinetic energy is a",
      "choices": {
        "0": "car sitting up on blocks",
        "1": "flag hanging on a flagpole",
        "2": "pillow leaning against the back of a chair",
        "3": "pendulum swinging in a grandfather clock"
      },
      "answer": "pendulum swinging in a grandfather clock"
    },
    "11": {
      "question": "Which of the following can be spread from one person to another?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "allergy",
        "1": "arthritis",
        "2": "hepatitis",
        "3": "epilepsy"
      },
      "answer": "hepatitis"
    },
    "12": {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a part of an atom?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "neutron",
        "1": "molecule",
        "2": "electron",
        "3": "proton"
      },
      "answer": "molecule"
    },
    "13": {
      "question": "The pancreas is a",
      "choices": {
        "0": "cell",
        "1": "gland",
        "2": "cancer",
        "3": "catalyst"
      },
      "answer": "gland"
    },
    "14": {
      "question": "Why do we see different areas of the sky during the Fall versus the Spring?",
      "choices": {
        "0": "the Moon blocking part of the sky",
        "1": "the daily rotation of Earth",
        "2": "Earth’s tilt and its orbiting around the Sun",
        "3": "stars’ extremely rapid motion in space"
      },
      "answer": "Earth’s tilt and its orbiting around the Sun"
    }
  }
}